#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/saitv (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Excel
PowerPoint
Microsoft Office

# Sai Teja Vallabhaneni

Data Scientist/Analyst - Seeking Entry Level Opportunities! Orange County, California Area

### Summary

Data Scientist offering 3+ years of experience in project work and freelance jobs. Bringing 1+ years of related experience strengthening company operations. Experience with executing data-driven solutions to increase efficiency, accuracy, and utility of internal data processing. Experienced at creating data regression models, using predictive data modeling, including assessing credit risks, digitizing records, analyzing data mining algorithms to deliver insights and implement action-oriented

solutions to complex business problems. Experienced in collecting, cleaning and organizing data to make it useful to both technical and non-technical team members. Proficient knowledge in machine learning, statistics, problem solving, and programming. Experienced in business operations and analytics tools for effective analyses of data.

## Experience

Verizon Wireless Solution Specialist March 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Chino Hills, California

#### Amazon

Operations and Logistics Associate November 2016 - August 2017 (10 months) Buena Park, California

California State University, Fullerton Undergraduate Researcher January 2014 - January 2017 (3 years 1 month) United States

St. Jude Medical Center Volunteer

April 2013 - August 2015 (2 years 5 months)

Fullerton

## Education

Claremont Graduate University

Master of Science - MS, Information Systems & Technology, Data Science and Analytics · (2017 - 2019)

California State University-Fullerton

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Biochemistry, Information Systems & Decision Sciences · (2011 - 2017)